[
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "12A_Don",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Don_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@12A_Don_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "12A_Shae",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Shae_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@12A_Shae_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "12A_Shazaan",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Shazaan_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@12A_Shazaan_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "12A_Tomira",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Tomira_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@12A_Tomira_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "12A_Chandu",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Chandu_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@12A_Chandu_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "12_01_MSQ_04_SerPayneBennett",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_04_TalktoPayne_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@12A_MSQ_04_TalktoPayne",
        "AchievementUnlock": "12A_PayneTalk01",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "12_02_MSQ_12_SerPayneBennett",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial_TalkTo_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial_TalkTo_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "12A_PayneTalk02",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "12_03_MSQ_10_Lochnir_Explains",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_10_Lochnir_Explains_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@12A_MSQ_10_Lochnir_Explains",
        "AchievementUnlock": "12A_LochnirTalk01",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "12_11_MSQ_15_GraceOMalley",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_TalkTo_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_TalkTo_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "12A_Grace15",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_TalkLochnir",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_TalkLochnir_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_TalkLochnir_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "12A_MSQ_17_YoungeGeiser",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_TalkTo_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_TalkTo_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "12A_MSQ_19_RegentJinJae",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla_TalkTo_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla_TalkTo_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "12A_Regent19",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "12_12_MSQ_15_GraceOMalley",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_Obj_Proposal_Next3_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_Obj_Proposal_Next3",
        "AchievementUnlock": "12A_Grace15A",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    }
]
